[
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is the name of Ross and Carol's son?",
    "answers": ["Ben", "Jack", "Charlie", "Max"],
    "correct": "Ben"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What was the name of Ross's first wife?",
    "answers": ["Susan", "Emily", "Rachel", "Carol"],
    "correct": "Carol"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is Chandler's middle name?",
    "answers": ["Muriel", "Michael", "Matthew", "Marcel"],
    "correct": "Muriel"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is the name of Phoebe's twin sister?",
    "answers": ["Ursula", "Monica", "Janice", "Rachel"],
    "correct": "Ursula"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What does Joey never share?",
    "answers": ["Food", "Money", "Clothes", "Secrets"],
    "correct": "Food"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What was the name of Rachel's hairless cat?",
    "answers": [
      "Mr. Whiskerson",
      "Mrs. Fluffy",
      "Mr. Bigglesworth",
      "Smelly Cat"
    ],
    "correct": "Mr. Whiskerson"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What was the name of Ross and Monica's dog when they were kids?",
    "answers": ["Chi-Chi", "LaPooh", "Marcel", "Clunkers"],
    "correct": "Chi-Chi"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is the name of Joey's stuffed penguin?",
    "answers": ["Hugsy", "Waddle", "Fluffy", "Snowball"],
    "correct": "Hugsy"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What fruit is Ross allergic to?",
    "answers": ["Kiwi", "Apple", "Banana", "Strawberry"],
    "correct": "Kiwi"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is the name of Joey's character on Days of Our Lives?",
    "answers": [
      "Dr. Drake Ramoray",
      "Dr. Michael Mitchell",
      "Dr. Ross Geller",
      "Dr. Richard Burke"
    ],
    "correct": "Dr. Drake Ramoray"
  },

  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Who was Monica's first kiss?",
    "answers": ["Ross", "Chandler", "Joey", "Richard"],
    "correct": "Ross"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What kind of uniform does Joey wear to Monica and Chandler's wedding?",
    "answers": ["Soldier", "Chef", "Cowboy", "Superman"],
    "correct": "Soldier"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What was the name of Ross's monkey?",
    "answers": ["Marcel", "Maurice", "Mike", "Melvin"],
    "correct": "Marcel"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What song makes Ross and Rachel's daughter Emma laugh for the first time?",
    "answers": [
      "Baby Got Back",
      "Twinkle Twinkle Little Star",
      "Smelly Cat",
      "I Like Big Butts"
    ],
    "correct": "Baby Got Back"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Which of Joey's sisters did Chandler kiss?",
    "answers": ["Mary Angela", "Mary Therese", "Dina", "Gina"],
    "correct": "Mary Angela"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is Rachel's favorite movie?",
    "answers": [
      "Weekend at Bernie's",
      "Pretty Woman",
      "Breakfast at Tiffany's",
      "Terminator"
    ],
    "correct": "Weekend at Bernie's"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is the name of Chandler's father's Las Vegas all-male burlesque?",
    "answers": [
      "Viva Las Gaygas",
      "Men of the Strip",
      "Boylesque",
      "Queer as Folk"
    ],
    "correct": "Viva Las Gaygas"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is the name of Joey's agent?",
    "answers": [
      "Estelle Leonard",
      "Janine Lacroix",
      "Nina Bookbinder",
      "Eddie Menuek"
    ],
    "correct": "Estelle Leonard"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Which friend gets stuck in an ATM vestibule with a supermodel?",
    "answers": ["Chandler", "Ross", "Joey", "Monica"],
    "correct": "Chandler"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is the name of Ross's second wife?",
    "answers": ["Emily", "Carol", "Rachel", "Susan"],
    "correct": "Emily"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What was the name of the diner where Monica worked as a waitress?",
    "answers": [
      "Moon Dance Diner",
      "Central Perk",
      "MacLaren's Pub",
      "Central Coffee Shop"
    ],
    "correct": "Moon Dance Diner"
  },

  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What does Rachel guess Chandler's job is?",
    "answers": ["Transponster", "Accountant", "Lawyer", "Actor"],
    "correct": "Transponster"
  },

  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Who officiates Monica and Chandler's wedding?",
    "answers": ["Joey", "Ross", "Chandler's dad", "Phoebe"],
    "correct": "Joey"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What fake name does Phoebe use?",
    "answers": [
      "Regina Phalange",
      "Princess Consuela",
      "Monica Bing",
      "Emily Waltham"
    ],
    "correct": "Regina Phalange"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is the name of Joey's boat?",
    "answers": ["Mr. Beaumont", "Little Dinghy", "The Chandler", "Duck Boat"],
    "correct": "Mr. Beaumont"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Which famous person does Ross claim to have 'came onto' while visiting Disneyland?",
    "answers": [
      "Isabella Rossellini",
      "Cindy Crawford",
      "Winona Ryder",
      "Christina Applegate"
    ],
    "correct": "Isabella Rossellini"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What does Phoebe find in her soda can?",
    "answers": ["A thumb", "A mouse", "A ring", "A toe"],
    "correct": "A thumb"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What store does Phoebe hate?",
    "answers": ["Pottery Barn", "IKEA", "Macy's", "Gap"],
    "correct": "Pottery Barn"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Who is Chandler's TV magazine always addressed to?",
    "answers": [
      "Miss Chanandler Bong",
      "Mr. Chandler Bing",
      "Mrs. Chanandler Bong",
      "Miss Chanandler Bong"
    ],
    "correct": "Miss Chanandler Bong"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What song makes Ross and Rachel's daughter Emma laugh for the first time?",
    "answers": [
      "Baby Got Back",
      "Twinkle Twinkle Little Star",
      "Smelly Cat",
      "I Like Big Butts"
    ],
    "correct": "Baby Got Back"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is the name of Joey's soap opera character?",
    "answers": [
      "Dr. Drake Ramoray",
      "Dr. Michael Mitchell",
      "Dr. Ross Geller",
      "Dr. Richard Burke"
    ],
    "correct": "Dr. Drake Ramoray"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Who is the last friend to find out about Monica and Chandler's relationship?",
    "answers": ["Ross", "Phoebe", "Joey", "Rachel"],
    "correct": "Ross"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Which friend was famously overweight as a teenager?",
    "answers": ["Monica", "Chandler", "Rachel", "Ross"],
    "correct": "Monica"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Which character famously said 'We were on a break'?",
    "answers": ["Ross", "Rachel", "Joey", "Chandler"],
    "correct": "Ross"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is Janice's catchphrase?",
    "answers": [
      "Oh. My. God.",
      "How you doin'?",
      "Could I BE any more...",
      "We were on a break"
    ],
    "correct": "Oh. My. God."
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Who got stuck in a pair of leather pants?",
    "answers": ["Ross", "Chandler", "Joey", "Rachel"],
    "correct": "Ross"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Who teaches Rachel and Ross's daughter to prank call people?",
    "answers": ["Joey", "Monica", "Chandler", "Phoebe"],
    "correct": "Joey"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Which character pretends to be a human encyclopedia?",
    "answers": ["Chandler", "Ross", "Rachel", "Joey"],
    "correct": "Joey"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Which character is known for their love of food?",
    "answers": ["Joey", "Monica", "Chandler", "Phoebe"],
    "correct": "Joey"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Who was married to a woman named Emily?",
    "answers": ["Ross", "Chandler", "Joey", "Monica"],
    "correct": "Ross"
  },

  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Which character famously said 'Pivot!'?",
    "answers": ["Ross", "Chandler", "Joey", "Rachel"],
    "correct": "Ross"
  },

  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is the name of the coffee shop where the friends frequently hang out?",
    "answers": ["Central Perk", "Central Park", "Central Cafe", "Central Bean"],
    "correct": "Central Perk"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What does Chandler's mom do for a living?",
    "answers": ["Erotic novelist", "Lawyer", "Chef", "Teacher"],
    "correct": "Erotic novelist"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Which friend lived on the streets as a teenager?",
    "answers": ["Phoebe", "Monica", "Rachel", "Joey"],
    "correct": "Phoebe"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What kind of car does Ross drive?",
    "answers": ["Porsche", "Ferrari", "BMW", "Mercedes"],
    "correct": "Porsche"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is the name of Rachel's sister who she babysits?",
    "answers": ["Amy", "Jill", "Nina", "Emily"],
    "correct": "Amy"
  },

  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Who officiates Phoebe and Mike's wedding?",
    "answers": ["Joey", "Ross", "Chandler", "Rachel"],
    "correct": "Joey"
  },

  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is Chandler Bing's job?",
    "answers": [
      "Statistical analysis and data reconfiguration",
      "Transponster",
      "Lawyer",
      "Actor"
    ],
    "correct": "Statistical analysis and data reconfiguration"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Who plays the character of Joey Tribbiani?",
    "answers": [
      "Matt LeBlanc",
      "David Schwimmer",
      "Matthew Perry",
      "James Michael Tyler"
    ],
    "correct": "Matt LeBlanc"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Who plays the character of Ross Geller?",
    "answers": [
      "David Schwimmer",
      "Matthew Perry",
      "Matt LeBlanc",
      "James Michael Tyler"
    ],
    "correct": "David Schwimmer"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is Joey's catchphrase?",
    "answers": [
      "How you doin'?",
      "Could I BE any more...",
      "We were on a break",
      "Oh. My. God."
    ],
    "correct": "How you doin'?"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "Which character famously said 'Oh. My. God.'?",
    "answers": ["Janice", "Joey", "Ross", "Rachel"],
    "correct": "Janice"
  },

  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What is Janice's catchphrase?",
    "answers": [
      "Oh. My. God.",
      "How you doin'?",
      "Could I BE any more...",
      "We were on a break"
    ],
    "correct": "Oh. My. God."
  },

  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b77",
    "question": "What fake name does Phoebe use?",
    "answers": [
      "Regina Phalange",
      "Princess Consuela",
      "Monica Bing",
      "Emily Waltham"
    ],
    "correct": "Regina Phalange"
  }
]
